<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Vancouver | My Canadian Experience]]></title>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/categories/vancouver/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-24T10:06:49-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://frans2526.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[François Versmissen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Vancouver]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/01/18/goodbye-vancouver/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-18T16:36:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/01/18/goodbye-vancouver</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After less than four months in Vancouver, I have to say goodbye to all my new friends that I met during my trip in Van. It's really difficult for me to do that because I met so many amazing people here but I want to move somewhere else.<br>
Somewhere, where I can see some snow and not all this rain everyday... (I'm in Canada not in Belgium :-D) <br> So I decide to go first in Toronto to see a canadian friend but before I had to do my farewell party in the Pint :-p
This name will be unforgettable for all my life.</p>

<p>Afterwards I want to go in Montreal or Quebec but I don't know yet... I like speaking in english and the english culture but I think that it will be easier for me to find a job in Quebec where I can speak french.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, I don't keep only a good memories of Van, this reason was my job in Wishpond, after only one month, I had already a bad impression of this place. My co-workers were funny and wonderful but the direction was totaly awfull and disrespectful.<br>
We were at least between 40 and 45 persons in a small office, I had the habit to say to my colleague that we were in "Auschwitz".
Imagine to work in a subway, it's the same but that was not the worst, they wanted always more "money" (for the Belgium people see the Luminis ads) and also I learned nothing except maybe "how you don't have to manage a company" :-D<br>
Just to remind you they didn't pay us for the work that we did there...</p>

<p>Now it's the past lets go Toronto!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 months]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/12/09/3-months/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-09T19:34:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/12/09/3-months</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi guys,</p>

<p>It's already 3 months I'm in Vancouver! That's starting to be long but I have a lot of work so I didn't feel all the time I spend here :-)
I find a job in <a href="http://corp.wishpond.com">Wishpond</a> where I'm Web Developer.<br>
When I arrived in October there were only 15 people and now I think we arrived at least 35 people! It's like my second family, we hang out every week to the WhiteSpot and it's always a good time there :-)</p>

<p>What's happened between my last post and now?<br>
A lot of party and hours of work :-p but except that some of my best friends left Vancouver to go back to their countries so I'm sad for that and also because it's the first time for me I wont spend christmas with my family.
The last Sunday I went to the Chrismas Parade with some friends that was really great and it's really tipical to see all the people parading in the street, it's like in the american movies. (I posted some pictures at the end of the post)<br></p>

<p>Yesterday, I went to Deep Cove because I've never been there and also that was a beautiful day, so we were walking in the forest
to the view point where we can see Deep Cove and Vancouver in the back. We saw also the snow on the top of the mountain that's great because it's something that I miss, it's the cold and the snow especially because the temperature here it's between 7C and 4C daily with rain the sunset it's at 4:00pm and the sunrise at 7:20am.</p>

<p>Chrismas is there !<br>
Here the Chrismas is everywhere and also earlier than in Belgium after Halloween it's directly Christmas... Business is Business.
My boss will organise a Christmas diner the next sunday for the company like in the american movie :-p</p>

<p>See you later and don't hesitate to write a comment,</p>

<p>Some pictures :</p>

<p>Chrismas Parade:
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/02122012384.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/02122012389.jpg">
After the parade:
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/02122012401.jpg">
Chrismas:
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/28112012371.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/29112012373.jpg">
Deep Cove:
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/08122012406.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/08122012420.jpg">
Stanley Park under the sunset:
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/24112012354.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/24112012356.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/24112012361.jpg">
Employee of the week (2 times :-p)
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/20112012351.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The adventure continue]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/10/21/the-adventure-continue/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-21T16:28:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/10/21/the-adventure-continue</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi guys !</p>

<p>Sorry for the delay but I was really busy :-p
I continue where I stopped so my first day of school I met some people but especially two who now are good friends Marie and Adam. Marie comes from Belgium and Adam comes from Barcelona.
I don't remember all the activity we did but one of my typical day in Tamwood was when I finished the school at 1:50pm Adam and I we visited some places of Vancouver with the sunshine :-p
I leaved my first homestay after 3 weeks because I had extended for two more weeks in Tamwood so they didn't keep me more longer so now I'm in a homesaty with two italian retired people, the homestay mum kook very well, she kooks every days pasta.</p>

<p>After 4 weeks there I needed to say goodbye of this amazing place and I started a marketing intership at Wishpond, it's a startup in the downtown of Vancouver and for the moment I working there.
I found an apartment with Adam in Vancouver but not in the downtown, it's a quite place near from the public transports(+-20 min to the downtown).
And because when I don't know what I can say I will talk about the weather :-D so here in Vancouver, all the month of September was incredible hot and sunny but now the weather change to "Raincouver" and the temperature is decrease each day. This weekend they starting to snow in Alberta, in the north and the east of the British Columbia.</p>

<p>The Next week we will celebrate Halloween and maybe we will go to a haunted house.</p>

<p>See you later and don't hesitate to write a comment,</p>

<p>Bye</p>

<p>NB: it's time for me to watching the Walking Dead on AMC :-D</p>

<p>Some pictures :</p>

<p><img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/16102012339.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_0009.JPG">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_0033.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_0054.JPG">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_0087.JPG">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_0299.JPG">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_0381.JPG"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/09/11/lets-go/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-11T20:07:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/09/11/lets-go</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello,
I leave Brussels the 5 september to Vancouver for one year. The flight to Montreal was good and when I arrived and passed the border. I went to the immigration office and a men ask me with enthusiasm "Pourquoi venez au Canada aujourd'hui ?". I was really suprise but in the good way of course. After I toke my Work &amp; Holiday Visa and my second fligth.
I sleept all the fligth to Vancouver so that was pretty cool when I arrived in Vancouver I was really tired yes it's true guys :-p so I sleept all the night ;-)</p>

<p>The day after I received all my documents from the agency and I toke my Social Insurance Number for working in Canada.
After I had gone to my first homestay but unfortunately I missed my homestay mum in the station so I walked between the Nanaimo station and my homestay. When I arrived there, there had nobody so I waited during 20 minutes outisde before they came back from a soccer game :-D but that was a sunny day so that was not really a big problem.
My room was huge with a TV and the familly is really friendly. In the family there are the mum Kathie, the french father Patrick and they're 3 kids Nik, Julian and Stefan. There is also an other student from Brazil Jaime. Everybody is so friendly, it's awesome !</p>

<p>After I had been to a swimming pool with Jaime, Stefan and Stefan friends. That was really cool because I had talked with Jaime and we went to the steam and in the hot tub.
The weekend finished, I went to the school "Tamwood Internationnal" when I met a lot of new friends from all around the world but especially Brazil, Japon and Spain (Catalogna(for you gyus :-D)). I think it's really great to meet ohter people and know the new culture.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
