<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Vancouver | My Canadian Experience]]></title>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/categories/vancouver/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-21T17:18:54-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://frans2526.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[François Versmissen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/09/11/lets-go/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-11T20:07:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2012/09/11/lets-go</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello,
I leave Brussels the 5 september to Vancouver for one year. The flight to Montreal was good and when I arrived and passed the border. I went to the immigration office and a men ask me with enthusiasm "Pourquoi venez au Canada aujourd'hui ?". I was really suprise but in the good way of course. After I toke my Work &amp; Holiday Visa and my second fligth.
I sleept all the fligth to Vancouver so that was pretty cool when I arrived in Vancouver I was really tired yes it's true guys :-p so I sleept all the night ;-)</p>

<p>The day after I received all my documents from the agency and I toke my Social Insurance Number for working in Canada.
After I had gone to my first homestay but unfortunately I missed my homestay mum in the station so I walked between the Nanaimo station and my homestay. When I arrived there, there had nobody so I waited during 20 minutes outisde before they came back from a soccer game :-D but that was a sunny day so that was not really a big problem.
My room was huge with a TV and the familly is really friendly. In the family there are the mum Kathie, the french father Patrick and they're 3 kids Nik, Julian and Stefan. There is also an other student from Brazil Jaime. Everybody is so friendly, it's awesome !</p>

<p>After I had been to a swimming pool with Jaime, Stefan and Stefan friends. That was really cool because I had talked with Jaime and we went to the steam and in the hot tub.
The weekend finished, I went to the school "Tamwood Internationnal" when I met a lot of new friends from all around the world but especially Brazil, Japon and Spain (Catalogna(for you gyus :-D)). I think it's really great to meet ohter people and know the new culture.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
