<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Toronto | My Canadian Experience]]></title>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/categories/toronto/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-23T22:26:27-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://frans2526.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[François Versmissen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold and snow in Toronto]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/01/26/cold-and-snow-in-toronto/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-26T17:12:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/01/26/cold-and-snow-in-toronto</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello and welcome in the cold!<br>
I'm in Toronto in my friend house, and outside it's freezing, it's -20C, that change from Vancouver with 6C...<br>
But I like that and I'm really happy to be here. My friend is a hockey referee so we went to an arena.
He had to work and I went with him to watch the three games, even if he said that wouldn't be good games, one of them was good and the two others was OK.</p>

<p>The next day we went to London, ON because he had a lesson there and he show me the university of London who are really amazing (I saw the university under the sun) that can modify my objectivity but that was a awesome to see this kind of university. It's totally different from the university in Belgium.</p>

<p>After all the trip, we stop in an lovely restaurant, the kind of restaurant that you can see in the border of the road in the US movie and I ate a delicious burger, I think the best of my life :-D<br>
After that, we went to his compatibility class, that wasn't really interristing for me. <br>
And when we had finished to work, we went to Waterloo, ON because it's the city of RIM, no I'm just kiding it's not for this reason, we went there to met one of his friend. That was really stunning because I was in Canada, speaking with two canadien english.<br>
I think this day is one of my favourite day of my trip even if that don't look really interesting.</p>

<p>Today I receive two apoitment in Montreal so I'll move so there and try to get a job...</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
