<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Toronto | My Canadian Experience]]></title>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/categories/toronto/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-24T10:06:49-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://frans2526.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[François Versmissen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold and snow in Toronto]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/01/26/cold-and-snow-in-toronto/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-26T17:12:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/01/26/cold-and-snow-in-toronto</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello and welcome in the cold!<br>
I'm in Toronto in my friend house, and outside it's freezing, it's -20C, that change from Vancouver with 6C...<br>
But I like that and I'm really happy to be here. My friend is a hockey referee so we went to an arena.
He had to work and I went with him to watch the three games, even if he said that wouldn't be good games, one of them was good and the other two were OK.</p>

<p>The next day we went to London, ON because he had to attend a lesson there and he showed me the university of London who is really amazing (I saw the university under the sun) that can modify my objectivity but it was a awesome to see this kind of university. It's totally different from the universities in Belgium.</p>

<p>At the end of the trip, we stopped in an lovely restaurant, the kind of restaurant that you can see on the border of the roads in the american movies and I ate a delicious burger, I think the best of my life :-D<br>
After that, we went to his compatibility class, that wasn't really interesting for me. <br>
And when we had finished working, we went to Waterloo, ON because it's the city of RIM, no I'm just kidding! This is not the reason, we went there to meet a friend of his. That was really stunning because I was in Canada, speaking with two canadiens in English.<br>
I think this day is one of my favourite day of my trip even if that doesn't sound really interesting.</p>

<p>Today I received two appointment in Montreal so I'll move there and I'll try to get a job...</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
