<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Montreal | My Canadian Experience]]></title>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/categories/montreal/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-23T22:26:27-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://frans2526.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[François Versmissen]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonjour Montreal]]></title>
    <link href="http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/03/23/bonjour-montreal/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-23T18:06:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://frans2526.github.com/blog/2013/03/23/bonjour-montreal</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Bonjour !<br>
I'm in Montreal since one big month but I didn't have the time to write some post.
So the big good news is I got a job in <a href="http://www.equationhumaine.co/" title="Equation Humaine">Equation Humaine</a> as a web developer. It's an really amazing place with a lot of space and great people. <br>
I found also a roommate in a nice place in Montreal, the people are friendly and it's nice because most of the people who live in the building are also student or young professional.<br>
We had a snow storm this week and so I saw one of the things that I wanted to see in Canada, a lot of snow :-D
But that was the last time this season, I think because now the temparture goes more in the positif.</p>

<p>The last weekend with two of my co-workers we went to the office to watch the first Formula 1 GP. At 11PM to 4AM and that was a little bit crazy but that was a really good moment. We had six screens with the two on the left the stats, on the middle top the weather on the bottom the live and on the rigth somes twitter feeds.</p>

<p>About the city, I think is more an "European" city and I can buy a lot of EU brand that I couldn't find in Van. The building are also more cachet than in Van and the city is smaller than Toronto so I prefere that. The public transport is really good, there are a lot of metro station every where and the price is cheaper than in Van 91$ vs 77$ in Montreal.</p>

<p>That's it for today ;-)</p>

<p>Montreal:
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_20130320_082444.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_20130307_201558.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_20130309_144337.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_20130309_152239.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_20130309_155615.jpg">
<img src="https://dl.dropbox.com/u/12732647/Photo/Canada%202012/IMG_20130309_171840.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
